Guide to the Stanford University, Plant Services Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Stanford University Building Plans (negative prints), Accession ARCH-1991-123
  - Old Chemistry Building - Outline Sketch of Walls (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Guy rope connect. for steel stack of Assay Lab. (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Reinforce Band for guy rope connect. ... (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Quadrangle - Logitudinal Section at the W. end of outer Quad. (01-380) Clinton Day Architect (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Quadrangle - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Quadrangle - Basement Plan - West end of Outer Quad. (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Quadrangle - Second Floor Plan - West end of Outer Quad. (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Quadrangle - Attic and Roof Plan - West end of Outer Quad. (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Natural Sciences Building - (01-460 & 01-420) Jacks Hall & Jordan Hall (Henry A. Schulze )- North Elevation (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Natural Sciences Building - South Elev. (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Natural Sciences Building - East Elev. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Natural Sciences Building - West Elev. (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Transverse Section (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Transverse Section (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of Basement (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of First Story (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of First Story (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of Seconf Story (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of Third Story (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of Roof (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Basement Plan (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Natural Sciences Building - First Story Plan (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Second Story Plan (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Third Story Plan (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Plan of Roof (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Drawings of Cast Iron Railings for Stairs and Landings (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Details of Cast Iron Newels; Cast and Wrought Iron Grills (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Natural Sciences Building - Sketch of Natural Science Buildings (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Proposed Hothouse to be built in rear of Botany Bldg. (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Removed 1906 (Shepley Rutan & Coolidge) (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Rear Elevation (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Main Memorial Arch - End Elev. & Transverse Section through Piers (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Transverse Sec. through Large Arch; end elev. (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Main Memorial Arch - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Roof, Fourth Floor, & Third Floor Plans (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Roof, Fourth Floor, & Third Floor Plans (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Plan of Windows in Ughtwell (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Main Memorial Arch - Sketch showing elev. of granite curb (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Stairway west rear exit of Assembly Hall (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Stairway west rear exit of Assembly Hall (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Stairway west rear exit of Assembly Hall (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Stairway west rear exit of Assembly Hall (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Stairway on Assembly Hall - Cast Iron Fittings for Railings (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Sketch of Mouldings around dome & proposed method supporting present Library (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Ubrary Doors (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Roof Plan for Fire-proofing present library (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Plan of Truss System (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Roof Plan for Library (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Stress Sheet of Roof Trusses for Fire-proofing Present Library (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Stress Sheet of Roof Trusses for Fire-proofing Present Library (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Ceiling Plan for fire-proofing present Ubrary (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - General Detail Drawing of Roof Truss (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Erection plan of proposed Library Ceiling (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Erection Diagram of proposed Library Roof (trusses & purlins) (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Erection Diagram of proposed Library Roof (ceilings joists and hangers) (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Roof for Ubrary (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Roof for Ubrary (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Roof for Ubrary (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Roof for Library (valleys) (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Roof for Library (trusses) (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Roof for Library (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Roof for Library - Ceiling Joists and Hangers (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - History & English Building (01-200) - Rear Exit (side & end elev.; plan) (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - History & English Building -Proposed change on Second Floor (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - History & English Building - Basement Plan (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - History & English Building - Area Steps to Building (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - History & English Building - plans & specs proposed table Women's Restroom (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - sketch to accompany order for doors (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - First Floor Plan - one story bldg. of South East End of Outer Quad (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Elevation (front and rear) and section (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building (01-260) - East Elevation (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - North Elevation (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Elecbical Building - West Elevation and Section (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Elecbical Building - Cross Section on line C.D. (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Basement Plan (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Attic and Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Iron Stairs (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - column, pillar, & girder (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - column elev. and detail (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Basement Plan (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Civil, Mechanical, & Electrical Building - Attic and Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Gateway - South East Comer - Plan (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Gateway - Drawing (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Memorial Church (01-500) (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Memorial Church - South Elevation 1906 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Memorial Church - North Elevation (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Memorial Church - Prayer Bench (End, Front, Back Elevation) (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Memorial Church - Sheathing for Roof (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Memorial Church Chapel 1909 - Outline Diagram of Elevations (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Memorial Church Chapel- Front Elev. Gallery, & Roof Truss (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Memorial Church Chapel - Plan of columns & girths at springline of roof trusses (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Memorial Church Chapel - Reinforcement of tower columns (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Memorial Church Chapel - Plan at Level of Galleries (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Memorial Church Chapel - Foundation Plan (girders & beams in main floor) (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Memorial Church Chapel- Glass Building (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Geology Comer (01-320) - Section on line A.B. (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Geology Comer - Section on line E.F. (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Geology Comer - Section on line C.D. - Side Elevation (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Geology Comer - Section on line C.D. - Side Elevation (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Geology Comer - Section of Arcade, First floor, Foundation (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Geology Comer - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Geology Comer - Second floor (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Geology Corner - Section of Arcade, First floor, Foundation (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Geology Comer - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Geology Comer - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Geology Corner - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Geology Corner - Attic Plan (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Geology Corner - Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Geology Comer - Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Geology Corner - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Geology Comer - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Geology Comer - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Geology Comer - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Geology Comer - Attic Plan (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Geology Comer - General Details - Doors (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Library Catalogue Room - Wooden Fonns for Concrete Stairway (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Civil Engineering and Geology Dept. (01-300,01-310,01-360) - First Aoor Plans; Front (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Rear & End Elevations; Section AB (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Arcade between SE & SW bldgs. - Plan of Foundations, Plan of Connecting Arcade, Elevation (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Arcade of SW Comer Bldg. (Geology) (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - SW Comer Bldg. - Foundation Plan of One Story Bldg.; Details of Footings (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - SW Comer Bldg. (1-360) - North and West Elevations; Section GH (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - SW Comer Bldg. - Floor Plan of One StOry Bldg. (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Plan of Entrance Portals (Quadrangle) (Box 4, Folder 225)
  - Plan of Entrance Portals (Quadrangle) (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - Plan of Entrance Portals (Quadrangle) (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - Plan of Entrance Portals (Quadrangle) - detail (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - Section through Arcade Entrance (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - Section through Main Arcade Entrance (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - Plans and Sections showing Roof Construction (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Elevation of triple arch between buildings (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - Elevation of Arches (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - Section through Arches (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - Elevations and plan of Drinking Fountain (near bldg. 020 & ?, 80 or 90) (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - Sway braces for arcades (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - Elevation and Plan of a Section of Bleachers (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - Bleachers for quarter mile track - Details of East Sections (Box 4, Folder 238)
  - Bleachers for quarter mile track -Bill of Materials (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - Bleachers for Football Field - Interior Details of Training House (Box 4, Folder 240)
  - Bleachers for Football Field - Plan of Training House (Box 4, Folder 241)
  - Plan of Proposed Athletic Fields (Box 4, Folder 242)
  - Toilet Rooms for Athletic Fields (Box 4, Folder 243)
  - Details and Elevations of Football Field Elements (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - Plan and Estimate of Excavation for Grading Supplementary Fba11 field (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Section AB and Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - East and South Elevation (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Plan of First Floor (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Sketch Plan for Laboratory Bldg. (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Roof Plan (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Foundation Plan and Details (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Detail of Column Base (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Cover for trench; Section AB (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Elev. of half truss at ends of bldg. (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - Plan of Laboratory (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - foundation plan & elev. - Ames and Westinghouse engines (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - foundation plan & elev. - ideal engine (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - foundation plan of gasoline engine (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - section of boiler room (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - found. plan - cross coup. engine (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - found. plan - return tubular boiler (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - Boiler House - Long. & Cross Section, Plan, Rear Elevation (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Boiler House - Plan (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Correct Drawing of Chimney (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Engine and Boiler House - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Sections and Plans for Pit of Gas Machine and Boiler House (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Arrangement of Piping for 416 H.P. B & W Boilers (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Boiler House Trusses (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Proposed Building for Power House - Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Proposed Building for Power House - North & South Elevation; Plan (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Proposed Building for Power House - Plan (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Proposed Building for Power House - Detail of Truss A (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Proposed Reconstruction of Power House - plan & elevations (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Proposed Building for Power House - Door and Sash Order (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Wood Working Shop - Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Wood Working Shop - Section and Side Elevation (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Wood Working Shop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Wood Working Shop - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Wood Working Shop - Second Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Wood Working Shop - Plans and Elevations (N. or S. E. or W.) (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Proposed Pattern Shop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Wood Working Shop - Sketch of Roof (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Proposed Pattern Shop - Half Elevation of Trusses A & E; Erection Plan (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Carpenters' and Plumbers' Workshop - End & Side Elev.; Half Section (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Carpenters' and Plumbers' Workshop - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Blacksmiths & Pipecutting Shop & Foundry - Foundation Plan & Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Blacksmiths & Pipecutting Shop & Foundry - Details of Footings (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Blacksmiths & Pipecutting Shop & Foundry - Detail of Truss (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Blacksmiths & Pipecutting Shop & Foundry - Details for Skylights (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Estimated Cost of Forge and Foundry Building (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Elevations, Plans and Sections (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Plan and Elevations (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Detail of truss A and shed roof (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Detail of truss B (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Detail of truss C (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Detail of truss D (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Detail of truss E (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Proposed Forge and Foundry Building - Details of roofing, brackets, chimney ... (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Addition to Machine Shop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Addition to Machine Shop - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Machine Shop - front & end elev.; plan, transverse section (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Partitions in Engine House - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Machine Shop - Engine House and Workshop (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Machine Shop - stonework (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Machine Shop - stonework and section of foundation (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Addition to Machine Shop - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Addition to Machine Shop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Addition to Machine Shop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Proposed MachIne Shop - Elevations and Plans (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Proposed Machine Shop - General Detail of Roof Truss (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Order for Mechanician Shop, elev. of door, window details (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Proposed Pattern Shop - Building Plan; window and door details (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Library Elevators -- Details of Hoisting Gear (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Library Elevators -- Details of Hoisting Gear (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Library Elevators - General Arrangement of Head Gear (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Library Elevators - General Arrangement of Head Gear (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Proposed Pattern Shop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Workshop - Elevations, Plan and Section (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Workshop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Workshop - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Proposed Plan for "cutting up of woodworking shop into classrooms" - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Proposed Plan for "cutting up of woodworking shop into classrooms" - Second Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Woodworking Shop - Section (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Woodworking Shop - Floor of loft and partitions (east end) (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Workshop - Roof Plan (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Workshop - Roof Plan (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Workshop - Section of Truss (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Bill of Details (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Pian of Metalurical Laboratory (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Comparative Bids (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Proposed Addtition to C.E. Bldg. - Plan of Walls (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Roof Trusses (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Roof Truss (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Roof Trusses (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Roof Trusses (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Roof Trusses (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Purlins and Angles (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Erection Plan (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Plan and Elevations (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Plan of Roof (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Stress Sheet for Roof Trusses (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - General Detail Drawing of Roof Truss (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Drawings of Corrugated Sheet Sheathing (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Detail of Windows, etc. (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - Proposed Pian for cutting up the drafting bldg. into Labs (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Detail plan of Main Lab. - Details of hoods (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Detail of Windows and Lockers (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Metallurgy Laboratory - Detail of Tables and Lockers (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - Proposed Restaurant - Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Proposed Restaurant - Side Elevation (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - Proposed Fire Truck House - Front Elev., First and Second Floor Plans (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Proposed Fire Truck House - Rear and Side E1ev. and Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Proposed Fire Truck House - One HIaf Front Elevation; Section (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - Design for Primary Schoolhouse - Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Design for Primary Schoolhouse - Side Elevation and section (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Design for Primary Schoolhouse - Footing Plan (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Design for Primary Schoolhouse - Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Design for Primary Schoolhouse - Roof Plan (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Details of Schoolhouse - Section throe front wall, part elev. showing interior finish (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Design for Primary Schoolhouse - Second Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - Cross Section (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Drawing and full size Detail of Iron Railings (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Longitudinal Section (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Foundation Plan (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Side Elevation (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Side Elevation (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Transverse Section (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Longitudinal Section (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Transverse Section (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Rear Elevation (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Plan (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - Proposed Plan for Mausoleum - Section ani Detail (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Planting Plan for Vicinity of Mausoleum (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Grading Plan for Grounds around Tomb (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Curbstones enclosing circles in Quadrangle - Elevation and Section (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Proposed Sandstone Base for Statue in Granite - Plan (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Retaining Wall around Palo Alto Tree (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Entrance Gate - Elevation (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - Entrance Gate - Plans, Elevations, Sections (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - Special Tile (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Special Tile (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Hip Tile (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - Finial (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - Mary Ann. (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - Denick (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Typical Plan for Fire Proof Rooms for oil Transformers (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - Main Entrance Lamps (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Bronze Standards for Terrace Walls (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Bronze Standards for East and West Walls (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Proposed Alterations to the Stable Buildings - Front Elevation (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Proposed Alterations to the Stable Buildings - First Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Proposed Alterations to the Stable Buildings - Second Floor Plan (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - Medical Department - Detail of Hood (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Medical Department - plan, detail of doors, plan and elev. of roof cages (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Medical Department - Plan of Sixth Floor, Detail of Glass Rack (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - Medical Department - Full Size detail of shelves and lockers (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Medical Department - Details of windows, shelves, and desks (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - Medical Department - Design of lockers (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - Library Catalogue Room - Wooden Forms for Concrete Stairway (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - Library Stairway - Sections (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - Counter Weigth for Library Elevators (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - Library Stairway - Sections (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - Arcades of Quadrangle - Plan for Fire Walls (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - Arcades of Quadrangle - Plan for Fire Walls; detail of door (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - Arcades of Quadrangle - Sway Braces (Box 4, Folder 407)
  - Waiting Station for Cars - Side and Front Elevations (Box 4, Folder 408)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory (02-510 and 02-520) - Plan of Floor (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Elevations (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Details of Yard Wall and Lecture Room Floor (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Sections and Details (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Plan of Foundation (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Elevations and Details of Deck (Box 4, Folder 414)